Towards the challenge, The wero. (spell it out) W. E. R. O.
The old ways are over. We carry the best of them with us, now shed the useless skins, and dress ourselves anew.
Begin the quest. Jump in the goon-gauge sisters and brothers!
Feet hard on the pedal. Forge ahead, but backward.
No! Forge ahead forward, snap off the rearview.
Hellbent, hell for leather, hell of a good time.
Existence is a montage, the palimpsest drives us forward, our purpose, poised collectively,
optimistic as we ride the change train, the goon train, the ghost train, the present train of thought.
Out of the underground and into the cities and surrounding lands my heroes. Escape!
The trains are the rhythm, the rhythm, the tool. Repetition is good. Repetition is good.
Let’s all hum the same tune together. Now that’s religion!
Stay on the tracks people. The methodology is established and understood.
The rains are a given. Without the patter, we are lost. It too carries us.
New trace elements are in the atmosphere. Fresh pollen is in the air.  Vox Populi.
Parhelion glow lights the way.